(THE YARNS)
Rapee died from inhaling too much helium gas.
The CCTV camera in front of the school was able to capture an image of a car.
Ms. Sookwan
Why?
I just left school at the same time that Raphipan, died.
Did I become a murderer?
This is the code, Sky, that I want Sky to help me decode.
Got it. It's so easy.
Medical science and the barriers to humanity.
This book is the key.
Cause of death Triyampawai ceremony.
(12 HOURS EARLIER)
(MOM, I WILL COME BACK LATE
DUE TO THE RAIN.)
Help!
Please help me.
Death, death again, death.
What to do?
Death again.
Death, death again, death, what to do?
- Get out, get out! Stay away from Sky's stuff!
- Sky!
Stay away from Sky's stuff!
Sky, Sky, it's me, Sky!
- Sky, it's me. It's me, Sky.
- Go out!
- Sky, this is Officer Lan!
- Stay away from Sky's stuff!
- Sky!
- Go out!
- Inspector.
- Get out!
Get out!
Stay away from Sky's stuff! Get out!
Hey, how did you get in
my daughter's room?
Get out! Get out now!
If you don't go out, I will tell the reporters
that you're harassing my daughter.
I saw the yarn on the ground
so I picked it up for her.
Get out!
I told you to get out.
- Get out!
- Stay away from Sky's stuff!
Um.
I'm about to call you now.
The seventh corpse.
There are two bodies?
- Nawin
- Yes, sir.
So the deceased was a Brahmin?
Yeah.
How can you be sure?
The body was burned like this.
The deceased's wallet was next to him.
And on his ID card, it says that
he was a Hinduism.
Is this the yarn?
Yes.
The culprit left it as usual.
The cause of death was likely due to burning.
And what about the other body?
This way.
The deceased was approximately seventeen years old.
It is initially assumed that
she died from physical assault.
Um.
There is a bruise on the neck.
That's probably it.
Yes, it is assumed that the victim
fought with the assailant.
But to be honest, it's really strange.
Previously, all victims had no history
of fighting back.
How can you be sure it's the same person?
I'm not sure at all, except that the body was found
in the same area at the same time.
But this girl's corpse is different
from all the previous corpses.
Oh, and most importantly, Inspector.
There is no yarn with this corpse.
Deliver the body to Anya immediately.
I will only listen to Anya's autopsy report.
Understood.
The deceased, Ms. Kamonwan Kaewkan, 17 years old.
The autopsy begins at 2:20 p.m.
There is a bruise on the neck
that looks like it was squeezed hard.
The victim was hit hard in the back
with a hard object.
Her hands were tensed as if she was holding onto something.
It's like she's grabbing on something.
- I got it!
- What is it?
The nails of the corpse were used to
scratch and injure the perpetrator.
What are you doing?
We are close to the truth,
it's right here.
The cause of death of the girl was strangled to death.
This case is not difficult, but the Brahmin's case...
The cause of death was indeed fire,
but where did the fire come from?
We didn't find any fuel that could cause the fire
to spread throughout the body to that extent.
May I have your permission?
The victim's phone has been unlocked.
What did you get?
Here it is.
What are they doing?
Knitting.
Knitting at the crime scene?
It shows that the girl
secretly saw the perpetrator killing the Brahmin.
She recorded the scene.
Did the girl die of witnessing the scene?
Yes.
This is why there was a fight
and there was no yarn with her body.
Because the murderer was not prepared.
But... I'm still confused.
Why did the fire suddenly start?
I knew it.
The perpetrator caused a spontaneous combustion,
or the phenomenon where the human body
spontaneously catches fire.
In this case,
the perpetrator used white phosphorus mixed with water
and poured it over the victim.
They mixed with water
because if it was phosphorus alone,
it would ignite in the air.
Turn oned the light to dry the water quickly.
And then there was only phosphorus
which is insoluble in water.
Phosphorus reacted with oxygen in the air and caused fire.
Produced a flame with a very high temperature.
No wonder there are yellow soot stains on the body.
- Plus it smells like garlic.
- So... weird.
It's so weird.
Why do they have to do this?
The murderer is very intelligent
and has a great knowledge of chemistry.
They had planned everything out
so that nothing was left behind.
But it was a mistake that someone saw them.
They didn't prepare to kill the girl.
Then the fight broke out.
That's it.
Have we got any evidence from the girl's body?
We're waiting for the DNA results.
Inspector.
Why do you need to solve the riddle?
The answer will be on the DNA anyway.
What is it, Lan?
Do you have any idea...
what I have to face while you're playing
mouse and rat with the killer?
Those crazy organizations...
they're raising
a counter-argument to my theory.
They claimed that my theory
was unable to help keep Thai people safe!
Take a look outside there.
In front of the house.
People come to protest against me every day.
No matter where I go,
people point at my face and scold me.
Although it was previously well-accepted.
People even used to support me
to run for prime minister.
As soon as I became the candidate,
this horrible crime happened.
And then the whole country put all the blame on me.
And did you know?
That my popularity has been dropping every day
since this crime happened.
I have worked hard to get you to handle this case.
Instead of helping me, you made me even worse.
- Sorry for the delay.
- Don't apologize to me!
You should hurry up
and arrest that psychopathic killer.
The Prime Minister of this country
must be me.
And I will pass a law to abort every baby with killer genes.
Understood.
I will close this case before the upcoming election day.
No!
You have to close it today! Right now!
You know, right?
Who paved the way for your success?
I never forget.
If you understand,
then you'd better arrest that killer.
No matter who they are.
And most importantly,
they must have killer genes
so that the society will trust me again, understand?
Go!
Nisa.
Nisa!
The murderer who brutally murdered
the pregnant wife of the Director-General
of the Crime Science Department has been arrested.
The investigation revealed
that he had killed more than five people.
The murderer confessed with a smile
that he killed for pleasure.
- Why did you do that?
- I'm evil! I killed them!
Uh, that's enough, sir.
You're drinking so much. It's not good.
Pirak.
My child...
They all died.
He has killer genes...
He took away all the people I loved.
Did you see him?
When he was caught,
he still laughed and said that he did it for amusement!
And in his eyes,
there was not even the slightest of remorse.
That's why you have to be strong and stand up to fight these violent people.
You are the only one.
You are the only expert in killer genes
You must rise and fight.
You must prevent these people
from having the chance to do evil again.
You don't want to see anyone get hurt
with the same loss as yours, right?
Ywah.
He made them die in agony.
It made my child
have no chance to see the world.
He took away the person I loved.
I will never forgive him.
Killer Genes.
All Thai citizens still have equal rights and freedoms as before.
And I promise that in five years from now,
if the crime growth rate does not decrease significantly,
I will be the one to propose the repeal of this Law.
Don't worry, bro.
I will take good care of Lan.
I will give him a bright future.
Only when you sign this paper,
and agree on every item in this contract.
Especially the one that states
that you cannot involve in Lan's life for good.
Here you are.
Lan, go sit next to your uncle, son.
From now on, you will stay with your uncle.
And don't be stubborn with your uncle.
Then I'll excuse myself first.
Thank you, once again.
Thank you.
How are you, Lan?
Do you like this house?
I like it, uncle.
Now, I am your dad. Call me dad.
Yes... Dad.
Good job
I promise you that I will take good care of you.
And will create a good future for you.
You will have a happy and comfy life...
But I ask for just one thing.
I want you to obey me.
And do not disappoint me.
Yes, Dad.
Very good.
Hey, get out!
- Get out. Don't mess with Sky's stuff.
- Sky, it's me, Sky.
It's good that we met.
So that you can stop thinking that
I'm the murderer.
Because on the night of the incident,
The police lieutenant was sitting
guarding the front of my house.
If I went out anywhere, I wouldn't be able to avoid the police lieutenant's watchful eye.
Alright.
And from now on, I want you to stay outside.
Don't ever enter my house.
I am very upset that you were rude
and went up to my daughter's room.
I need you here
to watch over Sky's safety
I didn't need you to get too close.
Even though Sky is not like everyone else,
Sky is still a woman.
Do you get what I'm trying to say?
I understand.
What's the matter, Officer?
Sky.
Yes, this is Sky. S-K-Y means the space above the Earth.
Why are you knocking on the window?
If you want to enter the house,
you have to knock on the door.
I...
I would like to apologize to Sky.
That day I went into your bedroom
without permission.
It's okay. Have you ever heard of...
"Being angry is stupid, being furious is crazy."
Sky is not angry at you, Officer.
Sky is smart.
Thanks, Sky.
Aren't you coming into the house?
Miss Sookwan doesn't allow me to enter.
But mom didn't order me anything.
Mom just doesn't want you to go upstairs,
especially my bedroom.
But I've already locked the room, so you can't get in.
And if you tie this thing up,
wherever you go, I will hear it.
It works.
Sky, let me ask you something.
Do you have this kind of yarn?
Yes.
I have this exact same color.
And... is it rare, Sky?
Is it only sold at your store
or is it available everywhere?
This type of yarn is ordinary yarn.
You can buy it anywhere.
Sky.
Yes?
- Can I go to the bathroom, please?
- Okay.
Go on, it's at the same place.
Officer? Officer?
Officer?
Oh.
Officer? Officer?
Officer?
Where are you, Officer?
Where have you been, Officer?
Why don't you wear shoes?
It just so happened thatI heard a strange noise
a moment ago, so I hurried to go check it out.
It turned out to be the sound of cats fighting.
So I stopped them.
I see.
But why didn't I hear the sound of the bell?
Here it is.
It's ringing.
Let's get inside.
Sky.
Yes?
- Whose shoes are those?
- Oh.
These are Skye's shoes.
Why did you ask?
Nothing. I think it's pretty.
I see.
(AUTISM COMMITS MURDER)
(WHY ARE YOU SURPRISED BY THE KILLER
WITH ASPERGER'S SYNDROME?)
(LIFE IMPRISONMENT FOR AUTISTIC MAN
WHO COMMITTED FEMICIDE.)
(AUTISTIC KID COMMITTED MATRICIDE)
Thank you, again.
My pleasure
Is this for me, Sky?
Sky.
If you give the lollipop to the Officer,
you run out of lollipop quota for this week.
Sky gives Officer the lollipop.
Thank you for saving me.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Nawin
I would like to request the CCTV footage
of Ms. Sookwan's neighborhood
the night of the latest incident.
What's up, Lan?
I would like to ask for the phone number
of a good psychiatrist.
So is there anything else?
Is this about Sky?
No, no, no.
Just get me the number first.
Okay, okay. I'll send you a LINE message.
Bye.
Hello.
Is this Dr. Lada?
Hi, sister.
Mark.
You're scaring the hell out of me.
Look.
Did you just peek at my phone?
-Ouch!
-Didn't you?
I just happened to see it.
Are you sure?
Do you want to go out to dinner with me?
I'll treat you.
No, I'm not hungry.
You'll be hungry when you get there.
I know what you're upset about. I can't help you.
But I can stay with you as a friend.
You can complain and whine about
anything or anyone as much as you want.
But...
No physical assault.
Smart-ass!
I'm not upset about what you think.
I'm annoyed that Lan
seems to be hiding something from me.
What is he hiding from you?
He always consults you about everything.
The serial murder case.
It seems like Lan already knows who did it,
but he wouldn't tell.
Normally, he tells you everything.
But this time he wouldn't.
It means that they must be someone
who he worries about.
He won't tell you until he is so sure of that.
But besides Ms. Sookwan
Lan never suspected anyone. Who could it be?
Grab something to eat with me, come on.
Let's figure this out.
- Hurry up, who could it be?
- I'm thinking.
Sky, you better keep your head inside,
it's dangerous.
You'll ruin your hair.
That's fine.
Sky likes messy hair.
Sky, if your hair is messy... you won't look pretty.
If my hair is messy, I won't look pretty?
I'm just kidding, Sky.
You are always pretty anyway.
But...
you told my mom that you'd go to work.
this is not the way to the police department.
It just so happens that
I'm going to take you to another place.
There is a hidden code.
Where? Sky likes to decode.
Just sit tight. We're almost there.
The sky is so beautiful.
Sky likes the sky.
Is there a code to decode here? Why is it so scary?
I'd like you to help me look into this.
Is there really a hidden code here?
Sky, don't be afraid.
You're with me, no need to be afraid.
Let's go.
Let's go inside.
Is it possible for a person to have
two or multiple personalities?
And each personality is completely different.
Yes, there is.
It's called multiple
personality disorder or multiple identity disorder.
Patients often have more than
one personality and switch between them.
Then... do they really remember who they are?
Normally, memory, perception, thoughts and feelings
are separated from each personality.
Some patients are unable to recognize
themselves in other personalities.
Sky.
Have you ever been here?
Never.
Sir.
The CCTV footage collected of Ms. Sookwan's
neighborhood on the night of the incident.
Sky.
Please think it through.
Think it through
whether you've been here before or not.
Sky.
Scary. Scary.
- Fire! Fire!
- Fire?
What's on fire, Sky?
What's on fire?
Where was the fire, Sky? Where was the fire?
Over there.
- Over there, at the tank.
- Where is it?
There's a fire at the tank over there.
Was there a fire over there, Sky?
Was there a fire over there?
Was anyone sitting there?
Was anyone sitting there, Sky?
There was. There was.
Who was that, Sky? Who was that, Sky?
Enough! Enough!
- Enough! Sky is scared.
- Sky! Sky! Sky!
Secondary personality often appears
when the patient is in a stressful situation
or receive mental pressure.
I'm sorry, Sky.
That I took you to such a scary place
That's okay.
Sky.
Let me ask you something.
How did you know that there was a fire there?
Even though you have never been there.
Sky...
It's okay, Sky.
Just take your time.
Think it through and tell me.
What did you want to tell me?
Sky...
Sky doesn't know.
Let's try again, Sky.
Sky...
have never been there
or you have been there
but you couldn't remember.
Sky.
Sky, would you like to have a lollipop first?
Would you like to have a lollipop, Sky?
Sky, have some weet first.
Sky, look over there.
There. Look at that.
What's up, An?
Lan.
The killer's DNA result is out.
The DNA doesn't match the criminal records.
If you're suspicious of Ms. Sookwan,
you must find a way to get her DNA to me.
And this DNA...
what else can I get the DNA sample besides hair?
The hair must be hair that does not fall out.
It must have roots.
Otherwise, it won't work.
Maybe a chewing gum,
nails, blood,
cigarette butt and a toothbrush.
Hello, Lan. Can you hear me?
- That's all for now.
- Lan?
Lan, wait a minute. Lan.
Do you want to test
the killer's DNA from the lollipop?
Isn't that possible?
You said you could use a toothbrush,
so this one should be fine, right?
The toothbrush has a rub-off action,
it hits the gums, the tongue, and the bulge of the cheeks.
But a lollipop is just for sucking,
it only has saliva.
The chance of DNA detection is very low.
But can we at least try it first?
I can try.
But you must tell me who the owner of this DNA is.
When the detection is complete,
please call me directly.
Hello, An.
I'm about to tell you about the lollipop.
Any progress?
- Can you detect it?
- Saliva can't detect anything.
But there was some tissue attached.
Even though it's small, it's usable.
So what are the test results?
The DNA on the lollipop and the killer's DNA
areninety-eight percent match.
The owner of the lollipop
is definitely the serial killer.
Lan, don't tell me that
the owner of the lollipop is...
Sky, you idiot!
How long are you going to be
a retard like this?
Who are you?
I am you.
I hid inside you and killed those people.
It's not true.
Sky didn't do it. Sky didn't kill.
I didn't kill anyone.
Then I killed them all, huh?
But I am you.
You are me.
Then how could you keep your hands clean?
Not true. Not true.
Then how did you see what happened?
How do you know
when someone is going to die?
If it weren't for you and me,
who the hell would know
how to decode all the riddles?
Sky didn't do it. Sky didn't do it.
This is not real!
You are the murderer.
- You are a murderer.
- Not true!
Sky didn't do it. Sky didn't do it.
Sky is a murderer.
You're a murderer, Sky.
You are a murderer!
No!
Sky dreamed.
Sky dreamed. Just a dream.
What are you doing here?
Why are there so many of you here?
I would like permission to search your house.
- You have no right. This is my house.
- This is a court order.
- Please collaborate.
- You don't have the right.
What are you going to do?
You don't have the right.
Officer!
No, no, no, no, no! Strangers are allowed to enter.
No entry allowed!
No entry. No entry.
Sky, let him in. He has a warrant.
He'll be gone in a minute, honey.
No, no. My mother taught me
not to let strangers into the house.
Officer, Officer, Officer,
please take your friends out.
- Take them out.
- Sky
Sky, listen to me.
I need to do it.
I would like permission to search your bedroom.
No, no, no, the police are not allowed
to enter my bedroom!
How can you enter my bedroom, Officer?
Do not enter my bedroom, Officer.
Please, Officer. Please!
Split up and search!
- Don't touch my child.
- Officer!
Sky.
Hello, my name is Pilanthorn.
I am a police officer.
Hello.
My name is Sky.
S-K-Y means the space above the Earth.
Sky, Sky, Sky.
You can step back a bit.
If you walk close to me like this,
other people will think that you are my boyfriend.
Not good. Not good.
Sky.
The Officer is not a stranger,
not just an acquaintance.
The Officer saved Sky's life,
so Sky considers you as a friend.
Sky gives Officer the lollipop.
Thank you for saving me.